A Guide to the Judy Project: African American History at Richmond Hill research papers, 2019-2022
Library of Virginia
- General (Box 5-6)
  - Zoom presentation, Womanist Wellness Workshop: Tilling the Soil, Exposing the Roots: Discovering OUr Ancestral Legacies, 2021 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Whole Truth History--Pam Smith at Virginia Theological Seminary, October 2022 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Brochure--Richmond Hill: The Judy Project and Mending Walls Transcending Walls (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - brochure--The Judy Project: Unearthing African American Stories at Richmond Hill, 2021 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Booklet--Seeing the Scars of Slavery in the Natural Environment: An Interpretive Guide to the Manchester Slave Trail Along the James River in Richmond, James River Park System (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Program--Dedication of Hearth Memorial to the Enslaved, William and Mary, 7 May 2022 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Brochure--Museum Guide Your History Museum Your History: Virginia Museum of History and Culture (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - The Old City Cemetery: A Quick Guide (Lynchburg) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - The Black History Committee of the Friends of the Thomas Balch Library of the Town of Leesburg, Virginia: Our History, Our Mission, our Ongoing Commitment (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cards--True Sons of Freedom, The Library of Virginia (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Poem--My Great Grandfather's Slaves by Wendell Berry (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Brochure--Cemeteries of Belmead Powhatan, Virginia (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Program--VCU Department of History Diploma Ceremony, 14 May 2022 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Brochure--John Jasper: Virginia's Celebrated Preacher (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Program--American Civil War Museum and Virginia Museum of History and Culture Present Legacies of Emancipation, 25 October 2019 (Box 6, Folder 16)